{
    "id": "1d76d7c442ae449fa3b5769985431abd",
    "title": "Possessive Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Let’s go to …………………. house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "she"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Is this book ....................................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "you",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "That house is ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "she"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you hear the mobile ring? I think it is .................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Can we go in .................................. car?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Look at that dog over there. It is ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Look at that house over the river. It is ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "them",
                "their",
                "theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This car is ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "our",
                "ours",
                "us"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Is this ...................................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "No, it is ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "she"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}